<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sport Events</string>
    <string name="loadingLabel">Loading…</string>

    <string name="event01Text">Chelsea manager Graham Potter said he has "nothing to say sorry for" after he was subjected to a hostile reception from Brighton fans before the Blues 4-1 Premier League defeat at Amex Stadium.
        \n\nPotter led Brighton to their highest ever top-flight finish of ninth last season before leaving the Seagulls for Stamford Bridge six games into the current campaign.
        \n\nThe 52-year-old was booed before kick-off by the home fans, who chanted "Potter, Potter, what\'s the score?" in the direction of the away dugout after Leandro Trossards strike and own goals from Ruben Loftus-Cheek and Trevoh Chalobah had given the hosts a comfortable half-time lead.
        \n\nAsked about the Brighton supporters animosity, Potter said: "People are entitled to their opinions. I think I did a good job at the club and left it in a good place.
        \n\n\"Once the crowd were so engaged it was a difficult one for us. The scoreline is a painful one.\"
        \n\nKai Havertz nodded in Conor Gallagher\'s exquisite cross to give the visitors hope, but Pascal Gross capped a miserable afternoon for Potter and his players with a close-range finish after Chelsea goalkeeper Edouard Mendy parried Julio Enciso\'s shot into the German\'s path.
    </string>

    <string name="event02Text">There is a simplicity to the thick forests and endless lakes of Finland - which are a source of great pride to its people.
        \n\nYou can see that in Valtteri Bottas eyes when he talks about the sense of calm they bring to him.
        \n\nThat geography is why so many of the Finnish sporting greats, such as Juha Kankkunen and Kimi Raikkonen, find their way into motorsport - forced as they are to drive a car from a pre-legal age just to get around.
        \n\nBut less so Finlands current number one driver, who began life getting across southern Finland\'s unforgiving parcours on a bike.
        \n\n"My daily commute to school, even if it was snowing or raining or whatever, was by bike," says Bottas.
        \n\n"For me it was a normal commute, so I didn\'t find it that hard - I got used to it and the wet weather."
    </string>

    <string name="event03Text">Audi has chosen Sauber as the team with which it will enter Formula 1 from the 2026 season.
        \n\nIn a long-expected deal, the German car giant is set to buy a stake in the Swiss team, making it Audi\'s factory entrant.
        \n\nAudi is designing an engine for its entry, which coincides with the introduction of F1\'s new power-unit regulations for 2026.
        \n\nSauber will race in 2024 and 2025 with its current engine supplier, Ferrari.
        \n\nAlfa Romeo is ending its branding of the team after 2023.
        \n\nFinn Rausing, chairman of Sauber\'s board of directors, said: "Audi is the best strategic partner for the Sauber Group.
        \n\n"It is clear that we share values and a vision, and we look forward to achieving our common goals in a strong and successful partnership."
        \n\nOliver Hoffmann, the Audi board member responsible for its F1 programme, said: "We are delighted to have gained such an experienced and competent partner for our ambitious Formula 1 project.
        \n\n"We already know the Sauber Group with its state-of-the-art facility and experienced team from previous collaborations and are convinced that together we will form a strong team."
        \n\nAudi is a part of the Volkswagen Group, which had planned to enter F1 in 2026 with Porsche as well.
        \n\nHowever, Porsche\'s plans to team up with Red Bull as an engine partner fell through after the team refused to give up its independence.
        \n\nWorld governing body the FIA said in a statement last week that Porsche was still in talks with F1 teams over a partnership.
        \n\nHowever, it remains to be seen how that would work, as Porsche does not yet have an engine - it had planned to partner with Red Bull\'s new powertrains division.
    </string>

    <string name="event04Text">What to focus on after a United States Grand Prix that produced probably the best race of the season, with three outstanding story lines?
        \n\nMax Verstappen fought back from an 11-second pit stop to pass his two biggest rivals and clinch a first constructors\' title in nine years for a team that had lost its leader and creator less than 24 hours before.
        \n\nLewis Hamilton came as close as he has so far this year to a win, only to succumb to the inevitable and lose out to the Verstappen steamroller in the end.
        \n\nAnd Fernando Alonso produced one of the drives of the season - one of the races of his long and illustrious career - to finish seventh in a car damaged in a 180mph crash in which it did a wheelie, smashed back into the ground and then a wall, and he dropped to the back of the field.
        \n\nJust writing that sentence about Alonso, what he achieved seems impossible, unbelievable. But let\'s start with Verstappen and Red Bull\'s crowning achievement.
    </string>

    <string name="event05Text">Donald Trump has claimed The Open\'s organisers want to bring the tournament back to his Turnberry course on the Ayrshire coast.
        \n\nThe championship, organised by the R&amp;A, has not been staged there since Stewart Cink\'s victory over Tom Watson in 2009.
        \n\nThe former US president bought the resort in 2014 and invested hundreds of millions of pounds renovating the hotel and redesigning the course.
        \n\n"I can tell you they want to come back," Trump told reporters after playing the pro-am at the LIV Golf Team Championship being held at the Trump Doral resort here in Miami.
        \n\n"The Open wants to come back. I think this will have to be sorted out first," he added, referring to the ongoing disputes over the breakaway LIV Golf tour.
        \n\n"It is rated the number one course in Europe now. We did a big surgery on Turnberry and it has gotten great reviews, even from people who hate me.
        \n\n"They want The Open to go back."
    </string>

    <string name="event06Text">
        Next year\'s Tour de France Femmes will feature a summit finish on the famous Col du Tourmalet.
        \n\nStage seven, covering 90km, will start in Lannemezan before climbing the Col d\'Aspin at 1,490m and then the Tourmalet at 2,115m.
        \n\nThe eight-stage race, which totals 956km, will run from July 23 to 30 and end with a 22km individual time trial.
        \n\nTeams have been expanded from six to seven riders.
        \n\nDutch rider Annemiek van Vleuten won the inaugural Tour de France Femmes this summer after the revived Women\'s Tour de France returned following a 33-year absence.
    </string>

    <string name="event07Text">It was an unexpected request.
        \n\nRelay team-mates might ask for a snappier handover or a slicker start, maybe even a pair of spikes to borrow at a stretch.
        \n\nBut, when Alex Haydock-Wilson\'s phone pinged this summer, Rio Mitcham wanted to borrow something else entirely. His name.
        \n\nThe pair went way back. They studied together. They raced against each other. They hung out as friends. However, Rio thought he had better check. After all, it could backfire on them both.
        \n\nHaydock-Wilson\'s phone lit up with a line of verse. "I\'m with the boys at Euro Champs I told Haydock please if we get this medal Can we share the champs."
        \n\nAt this stage they hadn\'t even set off for Munich but Mitcham, 23, was already polishing up a track about August\'s European Championships.
    </string>
</resources>